{
"cpp":[
    {
        "question"      :   "Q1: Do you think we had the patience to make a quiz for every language?",
        
        "choices"       :   [
                                "Yes",
                                "No",
                                "Maybe",
                                "Jeffrey Epstein did not kill himself"
                            ],
        "correct"       :   "No"
    }

],

"html5":[
    {
        "question"      :   "Q1: Do you think we had the patience to make a quiz for every language?",
        
        "choices"       :   [
                                "Yes",
                                "No",
                                "Maybe",
                                "Jeffrey Epstein did not kill himself"
                            ],
        "correct"       :   "No"
    }

],

"ruby":[
    {
        "question"      :   "Q1: Do you think we had the patience to make a quiz for every language?",
        
        "choices"       :   [
                                "Yes",
                                "No",
                                "Maybe",
                                "Jeffrey Epstein did not kill himself"
                            ],
        "correct"       :   "No"
    }

],

"go":[
    {
        "question"      :   "Q1: Do you think we had the patience to make a quiz for every language?",
        
        "choices"       :   [
                                "Yes",
                                "No",
                                "Maybe",
                                "Jeffrey Epstein did not kill himself"
                            ],
        "correct"       :   "No"
    }

],

"scala":[
    {
        "question"      :   "Q1: Do you think we had the patience to make a quiz for every language?",
        
        "choices"       :   [
                                "Yes",
                                "No",
                                "Maybe",
                                "Jeffrey Epstein did not kill himself"
                            ],
        "correct"       :   "No"
    }

],

"java":[
    {
        "question"      :   "Q1: Do you think we had the patience to make a quiz for every language?",
        
        "choices"       :   [
                                "Yes",
                                "No",
                                "Maybe",
                                "Jeffrey Epstein did not kill himself"
                            ],
        "correct"       :   "No"
    }

],

"c":[
    {
        "question"      :   "Q1:  An exception is __?",
        
        "choices"       :   [
                                "Run Time Error",
                                "Logical Error",
                                "Compiler Error",
                                "None of the Above"
                            ],
        "correct"       :   "Run Time Error"
    },
    {
        "question"      :   "Q2: Choose the correct order of evaluation,",
        
        "choices"       :   [
                                "Relational>Arthematic>Logical>Assignment",
                                "Arthematic>Relational>Logical>Assignment",
                                "Relational>Logical>Arthematic>Assignment",
                                "Assignment>Relational>Logical>Arthematic>"
                            ],
        "correct"       :   "Arthematic>Relational>Logical>Assignment"
    },
    {
        "question"      :   "Q3: What type of Language is C?",
        
        "choices"       :   [
                                "Interpreted",
                                "Hybrid",
                                "None of the Above",
                                "Compliled"
                            ],
        "correct"       :   "Compliled"
    },
    {
        "question"      :   "Q4: Identify the C compiler of UNIX.??",
        
        "choices"       :   [
                                "cc",
                                "borland",
                                "gcc",
                                "gpp"
                            ],
        "correct"       :   "gcc"
    },
    {
        "question"      :   "Q5: What do you mean by “int (*ptr)[10]”?",
        
        "choices"       :   [
                                "ptr is an array of pointersof to 10 integers",
                                "ptr is pointer to array of 10 integers",
                                "ptr is an array of 10 integers ",
                                "None of the Above"
                            ],
        "correct"       :   "ptr is pointer to array of 10 integers"
    }

],

"python":[
    {
        "question"      :   "What is a correct syntax to output \"Hello World\" in Python?",
        
        "choices"       :   [
                                "p(\"Hello World\")",
                                "echo \"Hello World\"",
                                "echo(\"Hello World\");",
                                "print(\"Hello World\")"
                            ],
        "correct"       :   "print(\"Hello World\")"
    },
    {
        "question"      :   "Q2: How do you insert COMMENTS in Python code?",
        
        "choices"       :   [
                                "/*this is a comment*/",
                                "#this is a comment",
                                "//this is a comment",
                                "--this is a comment"
                            ],
        "correct"       :   "#this is a comment"
    },
    {
        "question"      :   "Q3: Which one is NOT a legal variable name?",
        
        "choices"       :   [
                                "my_var",
                                "Myvar",
                                "_myvar",
                                "my-var"
                            ],
        "correct"       :   "my-var"
    },
    {
        "question"      :   "Q4: What is the correct syntax to output the type of a variable or object in Python?",
        
        "choices"       :   [
                                "print(typeof x)",
                                "print(type(x))",
                                "print(typeOf(x))",
                                "print(typeof(x))"
                            ],
        "correct"       :   "print(type(x))"
    },
    {
        "question"      :   "Q5: Which method can be used to remove any whitespace from both the beginning and the end of a string?",
        
        "choices"       :   [
                                "strip",
                                "trim()",
                                "len() ",
                                "ptrim()"
                            ],
        "correct"       :   "trim()"
    }

],

"js":[
    {
        "question"      :   "Inside which HTML element do we put the JavaScript?",
        
        "choices"       :   [
                                "<javascript>",
                                "<js>",
                                "<script>",
                                "<scripting>"
                            ],
        "correct"       :   "<script>"
    },
    {
        "question"      :   "Q2: How do you write \"Hello World\" in an alert box?",
        
        "choices"       :   [
                                "alertBox(Hello world);",
                                "msgbox(Hello World);",
                                "alert(Hello World);",
                                "msg(Hello World);"
                            ],
        "correct"       :   "alert(Hello World);"
    },
    {
        "question"      :   "Q3: How do you create a function in JavaScript?",
        
        "choices"       :   [
                                "function:func()",
                                "function func()",
                                "function =func()",
                                "function:=func()"
                            ],
        "correct"       :   "function func()"
    },
    {
        "question"      :   "Q4: How to write an IF statement in JavaScript?",
        
        "choices"       :   [
                                "if i=5",
                                "if i==5 then",
                                "if i-5 then",
                                "if(i==5)"
                            ],
        "correct"       :   "if(i==5)"
    },
    {
        "question"      :   "Q5: What is the correct way to write a JavaScript array?",
        
        "choices"       :   [
                                " var colors = [\"red\", \"green\", \"blue\"]",
                                " var colors = 1 = (\"red\"), 2 = (\"green\"), 3 = (\"blue\")",
                                " var colors = \"red\", \"green\", \"blue\"",
                                " var colors = (1:\"red\", 2:\"green\", 3:\"blue\")"
                            ],
        "correct"       :   " var colors = [\"red\", \"green\", \"blue\"]"
    }

]

}